Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[woman] I just never thought it
would be like this. you know?
[crying] I'm almost 40.
Men treat me like I'm invisible.
I've given up on
ever getting married
or even buying an apartment
because I've put all my money.
all my savings into IVF.
And I'm just so fucking tired.
[mouthing]
[woman] My friends. they
silently pity me. I can feel it.
I'm glad I'm not the only one.
[Siobhan] Oh. no.
she's the worst.
She's been coming
here for a few years
and it's the same pathetic
share every single time.
I know. it's like. "I get
it. your life sucks. but..."
- Maybe that's 'cause you suck.
- [laughs]
[chuckles] Do you
want to grab a drink?
[sighs] I'd love to. but I have
an audition in the morning.
Ooh. exciting. For what?
Some "feminist" horror
film written by a man.
When are they gonna let
us tell our own stories?
When they're all dead?
Here. Put your number in.
Do you know Dr. Hill?
No. Who's that?
The best fertility
doc in the city.
I'll text you his contact.
I-I actually really
like my doctor.
Are you pregnant yet?
[chuckles]
You're so nice.
There's nothing more important
than female friendship.
[announcer] Please welcome
Academy Award nominee...
You're gonna be okay.
The ambulance is here.
How did you know I would win?
[Dex] Are you okay?
[Anna] What the fuck
is he doing here?
You-you called him?
He is the baby's father.
You can ride with
me in the ambulance.
but don't fucking talk to me.
[gasps]
[shouts]
[Siobhan] I'll meet
you at the hospital.
[grunts]
I'm so proud of you.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
[siren wailing]
[screams]
[panting]
Shouldn't there be
a medic back here?
[screams]
I'm sure it's fine. honey.
Fuck!
[siren wailing]
Which hospital are
we taking her to?
Ma'am?
I need quiet in order to
drive the ambulance. sir.
I'm trying to help.
And you've been doing a
fantastic job of that so far.
[Anna] What's going on?
Ms. Alcott. are you...? Hey!
[gunshot]
[both scream]
[Dex] What the fuck?!
- What the fuck did you do?!
- [Anna screaming]
Aah! Aah.
[screams]
[siren wailing]
The baby's coming.
Fuck!
[screams]
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Shut the fuck up!
- Do something!
- Okay. Okay.
- [Anna screams]
- Okay.
[Anna sobbing]
[shouts]
Oh. my God.
- [crunching]
- [screams]
Fu...!
[Anna screams]
[screaming]
[screams. cries]
[Oscar clatters]
- [Dex groaning]
- [siren wailing]
[Anna whimpers. panting]
♪ ♪
[bhan]I want to make
a deal with you.
[chuckling]
Well. uh. I hate to tell you...
Ms. Corbyn.
but. uh. that's
not how this works.
I hate to tell you. Dr. Hill.
but that's exactly
how this will work.
[grunts] - I'm gonna give
you the life of your dreams.
I'm gonna send you
every high-profile
- and wealthy patient who will do anything for a baby.
- [grunting]
Spend anything for a baby.
You will become
the number one fertility
specialist in New York City
while always looking amazing.
And all you have to do
- is do exactly what I say.
- [groaning. panting]
How does that sound?
- Is that a yes?
- [grunts]
Yes. Yes.
[exhales]
Who are you?
I'm Siobhan Corbyn.
And I make my own rules.
[siren wailing]
[tires screeching]
[tires screech]
- [groans]
- [clapping]
Bravo. Bravo.
That was beautiful!
Oh!
[Dex groaning]
What the fuck is
wrong with you?!
- [panting]
- [Dex groans loudly]
Aw.
Did you know that
Kamal has a child?
- [Dex screams]
- Sorry. had a child.
I bet you didn't
even think to ask.
[Dex groaning. panting]
You selfish bitch.
- [Dex groaning. panting]
- [chuckles]
- [door opens]
- [Dex screaming]
- [door closes]
- Dex.
[wails]
- [panting]
- [wailing]
- [doors open]
- [gasps]
- [groaning]
- [shushing]
[grunting]
Stop it!
- [crying]
- [grunting]
- [choking]
[crying]
Stop it!
[sighs]
[Ivy] Whew.
I don't know about
you. but I personally
feel fine never hearing
that man speak again.
[sighs] Right?
[crying]
[screams]
[screaming]
[whispering voices]
Salve. o puer.
[groans loudly]
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
[cries] - These are the
last moments of your life
before you become a mother.
- [panting]
- Savor them.
Now
push!
[screams]
- [crying]
- Harder!
Domini nostri.
Salve
[crying] Harder than that!
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
- I can't.
- Salve. o puer.
Isn't it amazing that every
human being on this earth
was welcomed by the sound
of a woman screaming?
This is your night.
Now push!
[screaming]
[screams]
Salve...
[groaning]
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
[baby crying]
[panting]
Is he okay?
He's perfect.
[crying]
Let me hold him.
[crying continues]
[groans]
- ♪ Hush-a-by. baby ♪
- What are you doing?
- ♪ Baby not mine ♪
- [baby cooing]
♪ My woeful wail ♪
♪ Do you pity never? ♪
♪ Hush-a-bye. baby.
baby. not mine... ♪
Let me hold him!
[baby cooing]
You already are.
What?
You're holding what you chose.
and I'm holding what
you gave up for it.
No. no. no. no. no. I... I
didn't... I didn't mean that.
Oh. but you did.
You can't do this!
But we are.
[baby crying]
[gasps] Oh. Oh.
Okay.
You a hungry boy?
Here you go.
Oh. yes.
Ooh. he is a hungry
boy. [Laughs] Oh.
Oh. such a good boy.
Ooh. Oh.
Give him to me!
[groans softly]
[gasps]
What was that?
I didn't see anything.
[panting] Stop lying to me!
[spraying]
You'll feel so much better
once you just surrender
[distorted] and stop fighting.
[panting]
Stop!
Shh.
Stop it! [Crying]
- [muffled groaning]
- [shushing]
♪ And down will come Anna ♪
♪ Cradle and all. ♪
[baby cooing]
Good morning. sister.
Rise and shine.
It's a beautiful
day to make mayhem.
[singsongy] Mm. mm. mm.
I knew it.
And nobody believed me.
Where is my baby?!
- Shh.
[exhales]
- [whimpering]
- [soft laughter]
Hey. what's happening?!
Having trouble moving?
I brought your
wheelchair. Ms. Alcott.
- I don't need that.
- Oh. I'm afraid you do. Look.
- [laughter]
- She paralyzed you.
In the T-10 vertebra.
- You'll never walk again.
- Here. Let me help you.
No. don't touch me!
Very well.
What did I do to deserve this?
- Ooh.
- Oh.
Look. there's that
self-pity again.
"Wah-wah! Poor me."
You know exactly what you did.
You were selfish.
- Ambitious.
- Entitled.
- Conceited.
- Vain.
- [Sonia] Exhausting.
- In other words.
you were perfect.
Perfect for what?
[all] Our mission.
We recruit women who
want to have it all.
Career. marriage. motherhood.
We exploit that desire
for what we need.
In your case. we needed
something extra special.
What?
- We'll show you.
- Oh.
One.
[all] Two. Three!
- Yes!
- Yes.
[laughter]
[Nicolette] We hung all of
these paintings for you.
We know how much you like them.
[laughter]
- [voice 1] Slut!
- [voice 2] Has-been.
- [women screaming]
- [voice 3] Loser!
[voice 4] Cunt!
- [screaming]
- [overlapping voices]
Make it stop!
Oh. it never will. [Laughs]
You drank the Kool-Aid. darling.
Or rather. the B-12 vitamins.
[Nicolette] And the
gift bag of goodies.
And all those fertility shots
and progesterone suppositories.
And even my red lipstick.
And don't forget the
pickles and ice cream.
[Sonia] Why was the ice
cream in the fridge?
[Nicolette] Fuck you.
[Siobhan] Poor thing.
Don't you see?
This was all a part of the plan.
Welcome. At last.
We are so glad you're here.
How could you do this to me?!
Nothing has been
done to you. Anna.
This is all being done for you.
I can't walk!
[laughter]
Yeah. all right.
that part's a bummer.
but that's also kind of on you.
You reneged on our agreement.
- What? No. I didn't!
- You promised us a baby.
and then. you tried
to take him back.
Don't gaslight a
gas lighter. babe.
[sighs]
Why are my hands like this?!
Because you've got
blood on them. dum-dum.
[Ivy] Proverbially.
But don't worry. it'll go away.
[all] If you join us.
The women we target
always have a choice.
Join us and receive our gifts:
Eternal youth. beauty and power.
Or not.
and wander the world
ugly. aging and alone.
Just like your friend
Mavis Preecher.
And even though I had Nicolette
start stalking you in infancy
to implant all of the qualities
that we needed for you
to be pliant and perfect.
technically. you still
have a choice. too.
[owl screeches]
Welcome. Anna.
[laughs] I know. Surprise.
My little spies.
And my greatest
and longest fuck.
I only copulate with the
most depraved men I can find.
My Dexter. who was the
conduit of a miracle.
It shouldn't have been
possible. but 45 years ago
he was actually really hot
back then... I conceived.
And I assumed the baby would
be a creature like his cousins.
but he was born human.
I made Virginia
raise him as her own.
- What was she gonna say? No?
- [laughter]
- [crying]
- [Siobhan] And together.
we created the vessel
that would give us
the most powerful
creature of them all.
The baby you birthed.
[laughter]
[Anna screams]
Your dead husband is my son.
And the baby you carried
is the product of
his sperm and my egg.
He is three-quarters
me. [Laughs softly]
I mean. we used to have to use
magic to make our creatures.
IVF produces
miracles these days.
You're a monster.
Oh. no. babe.
I'm so much worse.
[baby crying]
- [gasps]
- [Siobhan] Somebody's awake.
Please. can I hold him?
Absolutely.
But if you hold
him. you join us.
And if you don't
want to. that's okay.
You'll just end up like
your friend Preech.
I mean. either way.
you'll always have him.
♪ ♪
- He can't wait to meet you.
So adorable.
Gather. my Delicates.
Salve. o puer.
Ave Satanas.
Vivant...
[gasping]
[Siobhan] You killed my son.
You told me to.
[Siobhan] That was a test.
You were Abraham
and he was Isaac.
[chuckles] And what
does that make me?
I killed the surrogate's
human twin for you.
I killed my own
daughter for you!
So sweet. But not good enough.
Will she resurrect?
She doesn't need to.
But don't worry. ladies.
I saved the part of my
son I really needed.
I will be able to keep making
special creatures like him.
incubated in her.
and in all of you.
until we fulfill our mission.
What fucking mission?!
Saving the world. stupid.
[laughter]
We're breeding
creatures who'll grow up
to have super abilities.
[Ashley] Super strength.
Super swiftness.
Super ruthlessness. [Chuckles]
And viciousness.
Our creatures will
restore humanity
to the greatness
intended for it.
[Siobhan] And the
ones made with my egg
and my son's sperm will
be the most powerful.
[Ashleigh] They'll be our Napoleons
deploying their brute brethren
to kill every man on the planet.
Except for the ones
we keep as sex slaves.
[laughter]
We'll finally have a matriarchy.
[all] Utopia.
It's not utopia if you have
to kill innocent people
to achieve it.
Sometimes you have
to snap a few necks
to do what's right.
Men are responsible for
destroying our ecosystem
as we speak.
We'll never recover
from the damage
- toxic masculinity has caused.
- [baby fussing]
Our only hope is to wipe out
the tyrannical
systems destroying us.
And implement a new order.
[Sonia] One of love
and sisterhood.
not oppression and machismo.
It will never work.
Oh. it will.
[Anna] According to you.
But who are you?
I am The Auteur. bitch.
[whispering voices chanting]
I run this world.
[baby fussing]
You have to hold him now.
Someone just died for you.
[whispering voices
continue chanting]
♪ ♪
[Siobhan] He's hungry.
It's feeding time.
[baby snarling]
[Siobhan] Prepare
Mama's nourishment.
[baby crying. growling]
[crying continues]
[Siobhan] You need to
see what you look like
the first time you nurse him.
[baby fussing]
♪ ♪
Careful.
His teeth are really sharp.
Ah!
Why is my milk red?
Because it's blood.
Why do you think he
loved that dead raccoon?
Oh. yes. you did.
Yes. you did.
It-it hurts.
- It's good for him.
- Ah!
I can't do this.
Didn't you want to be a mother?
Not like this.
Motherhood is never what
we think it will be.
[baby fussing]
It's so much more beautiful.
[exhales sharply]
I really thought that
you cared about me.
You comforted me.
You mothered me.
I trusted you.
I believed in you.
I loved you.
You're welcome.
How do you live with yourself?
Oh. sweetie. I'm
obsessed with myself.
Just get away from me!
I never will.
We're blood-bound.
Together forever.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[chatter continues]
What's wrong with you?
People will know you're here.
People will know you're here!
We see you. we hear you.
♪ Sooner or later
you're gonna be mine ♪
you're gonna be fine ♪
♪ Baby. it's time
that you faced it ♪
♪ I always get my man. ♪
Let me fetch our libations.
[baby gurgling]
♪ Sooner or later
you're gonna decide ♪
there's nowhere to hide ♪
[baby fussing]
♪ Baby. it's time. so why
waste it with chatter? ♪
♪ Let's settle ♪
♪ The matter ♪
♪ Baby. you're
mine on a platter ♪
[baby fussing]
[whispering] Salve.
o puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
[both] Salve. o
puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
- [baby fussing]
- Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
Only light can
snuff out the dark.
Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
[louder] Salve. o
puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
Salve. o puer. Ave Hestia.
Salve. o puer! Ave Hestia!
Vivant liberi Domini nostri!
[screams]
[whooshing]
[glass shatters]
♪ ♪
[baby fussing]
[baby crying]
♪ ♪
[crying]
[chuckles]
[whispering voice] Salve.
o puer. Ave Hestia.
Vivant liberi Domini nostri.
Salve. o puer. Ave Satanas.
♪ ♪
[baby crying]
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm